GAURI SHANKAR SHARMA

Studying BSc (Hons) Computing

■: 9816346714,
■: gaurisharma358@gmail.com

Q: Sundarharaincha-1, Morang, Province-1.

Gender : Male

Nationality: Nepal

SUMMARY

A confident Django web developer with more than 6 months of working experience along with a core skill of python and java programming language. Along with the SQL and NoSQL database management knowledge, I am always enthusiastic about enhancing my skills in the IT field as much as possible.

With my previous working experience as Cashier, photo and video editor, and web designer, I have developed a friendly and approachable persona with the customer which gives me more encouragement to apply for high-level posts.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cashier - Gorkha Department Store, Biratchowk Branch

Morang, Province-1

February 2017 - August 2017

Registering sales by scanning items, itemizing and totaling customer's purchases, and processing return transactions.

Photo And Video Editor - Utam Photo Studio

Morang, Province-1

March 2020 - January 2021

Photoshop editing for passport size photo, video editing for marriages video.

Junior Front-end Web Developer - Uplift Company

Kathmandu, Bagmati Province

January 2021 - Till Date

Front-end designing for websites with Django.

EDUCATION

Shree Janata Secondary School - SEE

(Completed With 3.55 GPA)

Morang, Province-1.

April 2016 - April 2017

Sukuna Secondary School - +2 In Science Faculty

Morang, Province-1.

July 2017 - May 2019

Softwarica College Of IT & E-commerce - BSc (Hons) Computing

(Completed 1st Semester With 74.07 %, 2nd Semester With 71.5 %, 3rd Semester With 80.75 %, And Just Completed 4rth Semester)

Kathmandu, Bagmati Province.

September 2019 - Till Date

AWARDS

- Shivprasad Ghimire Smriti Award, 2019: Awarded along with 10,000 rupees by ?Indrapur Jesij? for completing class 12 in science faculty with the highest GPA ?3.78?.
- SEE highest scorer certificate, 2017: Awarded by ?Shree Janata Secondary? school for completing SEE examination with the highest GPA ?3.55?.
- Class 6 first student certificate, 2014: Awarded by ?Edcucation Board Community Dulari Area? for scoring highest marks in the annual examination of class 6 conducted by ?Dulari Examination Board?.

SKILLS			
Python	Java		HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Bootstrap	Django		SQL
MongoDB, Graph DB	Tableau D	ata Visualization	Adobe XD Prototype Design
LANGUAGE			
Nepali	Khawas		English
HOBBIES			
Photo And Video Editing,	Supervising,	Video Gaming,	Yoga And
Exercise, Dancing,			
REFEREES			